heistit.com 2012-01-21

# PRIVACY POLICY | Heist It

**1\. OUR PRIVACY POLICY.**  
This privacy policy tells you how we may collect, use, and protect personal information about you. When you visit our website, you accept and agree to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy, i.e., you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this privacy policy.

**2\. MINORS.**  
We do not provide services or sell products to minors. If you are under the age of 18, you may use our website only with the permission and active involvement of a parent or legal guardian. If you are a minor, please do not provide other or us website visitors with any personal information. 

**3\. OUR TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE.**  
Our privacy policy is incorporated, part of, and subject to, the terms and conditions for the use of our website. You may view all of our terms and conditions on our website.

**4\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT.**  
As with most websites in the Internet, when you simply visit ours website, you automatically give us certain information. Such information may include your IP address, what website you visited prior to visiting our site and what site you visited when you left our site, the date and time you visited, information about your computer's operating system and the type of web browser that you are using. This basic information is automatically recorded when you visit our website. To obtain this information, we may use cookies, that is information that our website server automatically transfers to your computer. This information may be used to track your session on our website and may also be used to customize our website content for you as an individual. If you are using one of the common Internet web browsers, you can set your browser to either let you know when you receive a cookie or to deny cookie access to your computer.

We may also collect any information or data you provide us by posting it on our website or that you provide to us by e-mail. You always have the right to choose not to provide us with such information. If you elect to withhold any information or data we request, we may deny you access to some or all of the services or features at our website. If your transaction with our website involves payment by credit card, debit card, checks, money orders or third party online payment services, we will collect information related to the transaction as part of the course of doing business with you. Such information will include, but is not limited to, your billing address, telephone number, and other information necessary to the transaction.

**5\. WHAT WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION.**  
We may use information and data that we collect about you in operating our website and business activities, i.e., we may use this information and data to contact you regarding changes to our website, new services and features, special offers, or to resolve disputes, troubleshoot issues, and terms and conditions for using our website. Our policy is not give or share information or data about without your permission, subject to certain important exceptions, as follows: In any matter involving suspected illegal activity that may expose us to legal liability, we may in our sole discretion, or in compliance with any legally issued subpoena or court order, provide information in our possession about you to law enforcement or other government officials in connection with criminal or fraud investigations, or alleged intellectual property infringement. We may also disclose aggregate data about our visitors to our to advertisers or other third party vendors for marketing and promotional purposes. We do not disclose individually identifiable information.

From time to time, we may use such third parties to provide services or offers on our website. If a third party requests us to collect information about you, you will be notified. You will not be required to give any information or data to a third and we will restrict the manner in which such third party uses your information, i.e. they ill not be allowed to sell or give your information to others.

**6\. USER NAMES AND PASSWORDS.**  
To access certain areas of our website, you may be protected by a user name and a password. You should not provide your user name or password to anyone. When you enter a section of our website that requires your user name and password, you should log out when you leave, and you should also close out of your web browser completely and re-open it before viewing other sites on the Internet.

**7\. YOUR USE OF INFORMATION.**  
When you are on our website, if you obtain personally identifiable information about another website user, you do not have the right nor are you permitted to disclose this information to anyone else without the consent of the user _and_ our consent. Furthermore, any information you obtain from our website about us or other site users cannot be used by you or others to send spam, i.e. unsolicited commercial e-mail or to send unsolicited commercial communications utilizing our website or other communication systems.

**8\. YOUR VOLUNTARY DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES**.  
You may choose to provide your personal information or data to visitors to our website or to other third parties who are not our suppliers. You are cautioned when doing so that the privacy policies and customs of these third parties determine what is done with your information.

**9\. AUTORESPONDERS.**  
We may use autoresponders to communicate with you via e-mail. We use a verified opt-in system to protect your privacy for such communications and you have the option to opt-out of such communications using the links contained in each autoresponder message. If you have difficulties opting out, please contact us by sending e-mail to us at aperson (at) heistit.com, or by mail to the address indicated below.

**10\. POLICY CHANGES.**  
We may in our sole discretion change this policy from time to time. We will notify you of any such changes by a posting a notice on the home page of our website home page. If you have any comment or question, or disagree with any changes to this policy, please contact us by sending an e-mail to us at aperson (at) heistit.com, or by mail to the address indicated below. Any changes we make to this policy will not apply to information we have collected from you prior to making the changes. You should read this policy before each time you use visit our website.

You may contact us by mail addressed to:

**Heist It Inc**  
109 E. 17th Street, Suite 3641  
Cheyenne WY 82001

phone: 888-434-7810  
e-mail: copyright (at) heistit.com

Heist It Inc Privacy Policy 041411
